Privacy Policy  

=================

This website is operated by Digital Control Room Limited (“DCR”), a company registered in England and Wales, registration number 7634516.

DCR is committed to protecting your privacy. This Privacy Policy explains DCR’s policy for collecting and using any personal data you provide on this website.

Our Purpose and Approach
------------------------

We will only use personal data we collect on this website for legitimate business purposes. In particular, we will not sell, rent or trade it to third parties for marketing purposes without your express written consent.

We may use the personal data you provide us to deliver services to you, deal with your instructions to us, manage internal record keeping, and to facilitate and enhance our service offerings. We may also use the information to conduct research on the users of our services and to provide you with information about updates, offers, products and services which we believe will be of interest to you.

Security
--------

We are committed to the security of personal data.  We implement security safeguards designed to protect all data we collect process and store and regularly monitor our systems for potential security vulnerabilities and attacks.

As you may be aware, no data transmission over the Internet can be entirely secure. As a result, while we will always use reasonable endeavours to protect the personal information you provide to us, we cannot guarantee the security of your information

Cookies
-------

Please see our dedicated [Cookie Policy](https://www.digitalcontrolroom.com/cookie-policy).

Third Party Sites
-----------------

Where we provide hypertext links to other locations on the Internet, we do so for information purposes only.  We are not responsible for and do not verify or endorse the content or security of any other websites or pages linked from or linking to this website

Your Rights
-----------

You have the right to ask DCR not to process your personal data.  We will, on your request provide details of any personal information that we hold about you, correct any inaccuracies and/or cease to make use of your personal information for the above mentioned purposes. To ensure effective information security, we will require proof of identity from you prior to disclosing such information.

‘Unsubscribe’ Policy
--------------------

DCR may email or send by post details about services or bulletins we believe may be of interest to you unless you inform us otherwise. You may at any time unsubscribe to receiving this information by sending an email to [privacy@digitalcontrolroom.com](mailto:privacy@digitalcontrolroom.com).

Change, Modify or Correct Details
---------------------------------

If you change or require corrections to your contact details or other personal information, please send an email with the revised information to [privacy@digitalcontrolroom.com](mailto:privacy@digitalcontrolroom.com).

How to Contact Us
-----------------

For questions and concerns about this Policy or the personal data we process, please contact us at [privacy@digitalcontrolroom.com](mailto:privacy@digitalcontrolroom.com).

Revisions
---------

We reserve the right to revise this Privacy Policy or any part of it from time to time.  Please review it periodically for changes.

Who We Are
----------

Digital Control Room is an independent RegTech software company specialising in providing Governance Risk and Compliance (GRC) solutions and services to organisations across the globe

Useful Links
------------

DCR HQ
------

71-75 Shelton Street  
London  
WC2H 9JQ  
United Kingdom

Contact Us
----------

[+44 (0) 20 3836 8930](tel:+44 (0) 20 7129 8113)

Digital Control Room Limited
